Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one can stop us, we rise through the storm♪
♪لا أحد يستطيع إيقافنا، نحن ننهض من خلال العاصفة♪
♪Even bleeding and broken, we'll still push on♪
♪حتى مع النزيف والكسر، سنستمر في المضي قدمًا♪
♪The earth quakes with furious might♪
♪تهتز الأرض بقوة شديدة♪
♪I'll hold your hand and charge into the light♪
♪سأمسك بيدك وأتجه نحو النور♪
♪Adventurers, a new tale begins♪
♪المغامرون، تبدأ قصة جديدة♪
♪Brave hearts in the real world win♪
♪القلوب الشجاعة تفوز في العالم الحقيقي♪
♪Sparks fly when courage collides♪
♪تتطاير الشرر عندما تلتقي الشجاعة♪
♪Burning bright, our crystal tears ignite♪
♪تحترق بشدة، وتشتعل دموعنا البلورية♪
♪Above this city we stand tall♪
♪ فوق هذه المدينة نقف شامخين ♪
♪Flying wild, we're breaking every wall♪
♪نطير في البرية، ونكسر كل الجدران♪
♪Love's grand adventure, we'll conquer it all♪
♪مغامرة الحب الكبرى، سوف نتغلب عليها جميعًا♪
=Keeping Up with Beauty= (Adapted from "The Highborn Matron Reborn as the Pitiful Heiress")
=مواكبة الجمال= (مقتبس من "السيدة النبيلة التي ولدت من جديد وريثة بائسة")
=Episode 7=
=الحلقة 7=
(This is the Fu family's Jiangxing Hotel.)
(هذا هو فندق جيانجشينغ لعائلة فو .)
Mr. Liu, please let me explain.
السيد ليو، من فضلك اسمح لي أن أشرح.
Our hotel follows
فندقنا يتبع
its own standardized management procedures.
إجراءات الإدارة الموحدة الخاصة بها .
When I was deputy manager,
عندما كنت نائب المدير،
the lobby operated under the same system.
وكان اللوبي يعمل تحت نفس النظام.
You can't just come in and change things.
لا يمكنك أن تأتي وتغير الأشياء فقط.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Listen, Wang.
إستمع، وانغ.
Let me make this clear.
دعني أوضح هذا.
I was sent here by Mr. Gu.
لقد تم إرسالي إلى هنا من قبل السيد جو.
My orders represent his orders.
أوامري تمثل أوامره.
People like you
الناس مثلك
should be grateful
ينبغي أن يكون شاكرا
just to keep your jobs.
فقط للحفاظ على وظائفكم.
Stop questioning my arrangements.
توقف عن التشكيك في ترتيباتي.
And you're not even a deputy manager.
وأنت لست حتى نائب المدير.
Just a lobby manager.
مجرد مدير لوبي.
Who do you think you are to challenge me?
من تعتقد نفسك حتى تتحداني؟
Miss.
يفتقد.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
Chenyu.
لك.
Don't you get what Yunyun meant?
هل لم تفهم ما يقصده يونيون؟
In every drama, when she says "I choose you,"
في كل دراما، عندما تقول "أختارك"،
it means
هذا يعني
she likes you.
إنها معجبة بك.
She's basically confessing her love, just rounded up.
إنها تعترف في الأساس بحبها، ولكن بشكل مختصر.
"I choose you."
"اخترتك."
I think whatever happened between her and Yansheng is already in the past.
أعتقد أن كل ما حدث بينها وبين يانشينغ أصبح في الماضي بالفعل.
Now her heart belongs only to you.
الآن قلبها ملك لك فقط.
Why
لماذا
don't you try being with her?
لا تحاول أن تكون معها؟
Mind your manners.
انتبه لأخلاقك.
You're my assistant intern now.
أنت مساعدي المتدرب الآن.
Watch your words and behaviour.
راقب كلماتك وسلوكك.
You really feel nothing?
هل تشعر حقا بأي شيء؟
Gu Shiqi.
قو شيكي.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
Mr. Fu was right here when...
وكان السيد فو هنا عندما...
Dad.
أب.
You wanted to see me?
هل تريد رؤيتي؟
Yunyun,
يونيون،
this jade pendant
هذه القلادة اليشمية
has been our Fu family's heirloom for a thousand years.
لقد كانت إرثًا لعائلتنا فو لمدة ألف عام.
Legend says it can turn fate around
تقول الأسطورة أنه يمكن أن يقلب القدر
in times of danger.
في أوقات الخطر.
Keep it safe with you
احتفظ بها آمنة معك
and carry it always.
وحملها دائما.
It will protect you from harm.
سيحميك من الأذى.
That's amazing.
هذا مدهش.
Why are you suddenly giving it to me?
لماذا تعطيها لي فجأة؟
There's some trouble at my company.
هناك بعض المشاكل في شركتي.
So I want you to keep it safe for now.
لذلك أريدك أن تحافظ على أمانه في الوقت الحالي.
Carry it with you at all times.
احملها معك في جميع الأوقات.
It will protect you from harm.
سيحميك من الأذى.
Dad.
أب.
What happened to the company?
ماذا حدث للشركة؟
Is it serious?
هل هو خطير؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
You don't need to worry
لا داعي للقلق
and don't listen to rumors outside.
ولا تستمع إلى الشائعات في الخارج.
I'll take care of everything soon.
سأعتني بكل شيء قريبا.
But...
لكن...
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Should I call an ambulance?
هل يجب علي أن أتصل بالإسعاف؟
Quick, make the call!
سريعًا، قم بإجراء المكالمة!
Dad, open your eyes and look at me!
أبي افتح عينيك وانظر إلي!
Dad, it's me, Yunyun!
أبي، أنا يون يون!
You love me the most!
أنت تحبني كثيرًا!
Please open your eyes and look at me!
من فضلك افتح عينيك وانظر إلي!
Someone help!
ساعدوني يا أحد!
Save him!
أنقذه!
Help!
يساعد!
Call someone, now!
اتصل بشخص ما الآن!
Please, someone come!
من فضلك، يأتي أحد!
Don't look!
لا تنظر!
Dad!
أب!
Stop taking photos!
توقف عن التقاط الصور!
Don't look!
لا تنظر!
(Jiangxing Hotel Acquisition Contract) Now creditors are everywhere.
(عقد الاستحواذ على فندق جيانجشينغ) الآن الدائنون في كل مكان.
The Fu family's finances have collapsed.
انهارت مالية عائلة فو.
You can't possibly fill such a gap.
من غير الممكن أن تملأ مثل هذه الفجوة.
Sign the contract
توقيع العقد
and sell Jiangxing Hotel to me.
وبيع فندق جيانجشينغ لي.
It'll get you through this crisis.
سيساعدك على تجاوز هذه الأزمة.
My father
والدي
really took his own life?
هل انتحر حقا؟
I'm sorry for Mr. Fu's passing.
أنا آسف لوفاة السيد فو.
Jiangxing Hotel
فندق جيانغشينغ
was my father's lifelong work.
كان هذا عمل والدي طيلة حياته.
I can't sell it.
لا أستطيع بيعه.
Will you just watch Jiangxing Hotel collapse?
هل ستشاهد انهيار فندق جيانجشينغ؟
I give you my word.
أعطيك كلمتي.
I'll preserve its name and reputation.
سأحافظ على اسمها وسمعتها.
I'll treat the long-time staff with respect,
سأعامل الموظفين القدامى باحترام،
just as your father did.
تمامًا كما فعل والدك.
(Signature of legal representative: Fu Yunyun)
(توقيع الممثل القانوني: فو يون يون)
(Dad,)
(أب،)
(one day,)
(يوم واحد،)
(I'll take the hotel back.)
(سوف ارجع الفندق)
Looking forward to working with you.
نتطلع للعمل معك.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Please don't be too sad.
من فضلك لا تحزن كثيرا.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
you sold the hotel
لقد بعت الفندق
to keep JiangXing Hotel alive.
للحفاظ على فندق JiangXing على قيد الحياة.
Mr. Fu in heaven
السيد فو في الجنة
would understand.
سوف أفهم.
I've worked at JiangXing for over ten years.
لقد عملت في JiangXing لأكثر من عشر سنوات.
To be honest,
صراحة،
I watched you grow up.
لقد شاهدتك تكبر.
There's something I must say today.
هناك شيئا يجب أن أقوله اليوم.
Miss.
يفتقد.
You must be cautious of the Gu family.
يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا من عائلة جو.
When the Fu family suddenly collapsed,
عندما انهارت عائلة فو فجأة،
the Gu family profited.
استفادت عائلة جو.
Can things really be that coincidental?
هل يمكن للأشياء أن تكون مصادفة حقا؟
Also,
أيضًا،
on the day your father passed,
في اليوم الذي توفي فيه والدك،
someone saw Gu Chenyu at the hotel.
لقد رأى شخص ما Gu Chenyu في الفندق.
Maybe
ربما
Mr. Fu's death...
موت السيد فو...
Anyway,
على أي حال،
Gu Chenyu isn't as simple as he looks.
غو تشين يو ليس بسيطًا كما يبدو.
Stay away from him.
ابتعد عنه
I understand.
أفهم.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
Mr. Wang.
السيد وانغ.
I'm glad you're all right.
أنا سعيد لأنك بخير.
(Could Gu Chenyu really have caused Fu Yunyun's father's death?)
(هل كان من الممكن حقًا أن يكون Gu Chenyu هو السبب في وفاة والد Fu Yunyun؟)
(This hotel is filled with Fu Yunyun's memories.)
(هذا الفندق مليء بذكريات فو يون يون.)
(My head's a mess.)
(رأسي في حالة فوضى.)
Our hotel restaurant here,
مطعم فندقنا هنا،
after three months of improvements by me,
بعد ثلاثة أشهر من التحسن من جانبي،
I added medicinal cuisine
أضفت مأكولات طبية
and nourishing hotpot to the menu.
وإضافة طبق ساخن مغذي إلى القائمة.
Since the changes,
منذ التغييرات،
business has been booming.
لقد كانت الأعمال مزدهرة.
It's packed every day.
إنه مزدحم كل يوم.
Sister-in-law...
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة...
Yunyun.
يونيون.
Inspect this place for me.
تفقد هذا المكان بالنسبة لي.
All right.
حسنًا.
Come on, let's check over there.
هيا، دعونا نتحقق من هناك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Do you have a moment now?
هل لديك لحظة الآن؟
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Duplicity.
ازدواجية.
(Was it really him who drove Fu Yunyun's father to death?)
(هل كان هو حقًا من قاد والد فو يون يون إلى الموت؟)
(Maybe)
(ربما)
(I should just ask him directly.)
(ينبغي لي أن أسأله مباشرة.)
Are you
أنت
feeling any better now?
هل تشعر بتحسن الآن؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Then
ثم
maybe I should head back first.
ربما يجب علي أن أعود أولاً.
Wait.
انتظر.
I brought you somewhere.
لقد أحضرتك إلى مكان ما.
Jiangxing Hotel was built by your father's own hands.
تم بناء فندق Jiangxing على يد والدك.
It must hold many memories for you.
يجب أن يحمل الكثير من الذكريات بالنسبة لك.
Everything from your family is still there.
كل شيء من عائلتك لا يزال هناك.
You can visit whenever you wish.
يمكنك الزيارة في أي وقت تريد.
You brought me here
لقد احضرتني هنا
just to tell me this?
فقط لتخبرني بهذا؟
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Gu!
ل!
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Miss?
يفتقد؟
Ever since the Gu family
منذ عائلة جو
took over Jiangxing Hotel,
استولى على فندق جيانجشينغ،
the old staff
الموظفين القدامى
have been demoted,
لقد تم تخفيض رتبتهم،
or outright dismissed.
أو تم رفضه تماما.
I've worked here nearly my whole life.
لقد عملت هنا طيلة حياتي تقريبًا.
Now I'm almost at retirement age
الآن أنا على وشك سن التقاعد
and they're firing me?
وهم يطردونني؟
Gu!
ل!
You'll get what's coming to you!
سوف تحصل على ما يستحقه!
♪Words I can't say linger on my tongue♪
♪الكلمات التي لا أستطيع قولها تبقى على لساني♪
♪Each time you're near, my heartbeat runs♪
♪في كل مرة تكون بالقرب، ينبض قلبي♪
♪Cold nights glow with gentle stars above♪
♪الليالي الباردة تتوهج بالنجوم اللطيفة في الأعلى♪
♪My silent thoughts stretch long like dreams of love♪
♪أفكاري الصامتة تمتد طويلاً مثل أحلام الحب♪
♪How do I hide these feelings so faint and shy♪
♪كيف أخفي هذه المشاعر بهذا القدر من الخجل والضعف♪
♪When I meet you again, warmth flows quietly by♪
♪عندما ألتقي بك مرة أخرى، يتدفق الدفء بهدوء♪
♪My eyes can't help but turn your way♪
♪لا يمكن لعيني إلا أن تتجه نحوك♪
♪I close them tight, pretending all is the same♪
♪أغلقهم بإحكام، وأتظاهر بأن كل شيء متشابه♪
♪The wind brushes softly by♪
♪تمر الرياح برفق♪
♪Carrying half of my sigh♪
♪أحمل نصف تنهيدة♪
♪I walk a while, then glance behind♪
♪أمشي لفترة، ثم أنظر خلفي♪
♪You bring back warmth I thought I'd lost♪
♪لقد أعادت لي الدفء الذي اعتقدت أنني فقدته♪
♪My pain quietly thaws♪
♪يذوب ألمي بهدوء♪
♪And in silence, loneliness fades away♪
♪وفي الصمت يتلاشى الشعور بالوحدة♪
♪Because you are my light in the dark♪
♪لأنك نوري في الظلام♪
♪I'll be your sun when winter feels too hard♪
♪سأكون شمسك عندما يصبح الشتاء قاسيًا جدًا♪
♪We shine for each other through the quiet and the loneliness♪
♪نحن نتألق لبعضنا البعض من خلال الهدوء والوحدة♪
♪You are the warmest light in all my world♪
♪أنت أدفأ ضوء في عالمي كله♪